National Capital Parks (NCP) Photograph Collection P034
Stage
National Capital Parks (NCP) Photograph Collection
1863-1961
Stage
P034
4 Linear feet
Biographical / Historical
Originating at the turn of the 20th century as the Office of Public Buildings and grounds, in 1925 the name was changed to Office of Public Buildings and Public Parks of the National Capital ("National Capital Parks" for short as the majority of images are stamped). On August 10, 1933 NCP became a unit of the National Park Service.
Custodial History
There is no deed of gift for this collection and it is uncertain how the library acquired these photographs.
Scope and Contents
While the collection consists of images from 1863 to 1972, the majority range from the 1930s to 1950s. The collection is broken down into forty series categories that document places, events and people associated with the National Capital Parks, a unit of the National Park Service since 1933.
- Aerial Views
  - Aerial Views, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    General
    Most photos labeled or stamped "file copy"
  - Aerial Views, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Analostan Island
  - Proposed Gas Works (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Arlington National Cemetery
  - Armistice Day, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Armistice Day, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    FDR, Lucy Monroe
  - Armistice Day, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    FDR, John Pershing
  - Armistice Day, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    FDR
  - Armistice Day, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Armistice Day, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Harry Truman
  - Armistice Day, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Armistice Day, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Armistice Day, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Dwight Eisenhower
  - Burial, 1921-1947 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Easter Service, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Eleanor Roosevelt
  - Gravesites, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    William H. Jackson,Robert E. Peary
  - Memorial Amphitheater, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Memorial Day, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Brehon Somervell
  - Memorial Day, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    Rev. Angus Dun, Tom Connally
  - Memorial Day, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Memorial Day, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Memorial Day, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Memorial Drive Entrance (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Relief Projects, Public Works Administration, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Tomb of the Unknown Soldier (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Wreath Laying, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    Order of Founders and Patriots of America
- Bridges
  - Great Falls, Proposed Bridge (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - M Street Southeast, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Buildings
  - Church of the Pilgrim, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Demolished Structure, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Frederick Douglas House, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Legations and Embassies, ca. (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - United States Capitol, 1863 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    Copy of original
  - United States Department of Agriculture (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Watergate Floating Stage, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - White House - East Room (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Civilian Conservation Corps (CCC)
  - Baseball Game, 1934 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Columbia Island Grading, 1936 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Camp Construction (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Construction Progress, 1933 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Fort Dupont - Construction Progress, 1934 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Fort Dupont - Construction Progress, 1935 February-1935 March (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Fort Dupont - Construction Progress, 1935 June (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Fort Dupont - Construction Progress, 1935 July (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Fort Dupont - Construction Progress, 1935 September (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Fort Dupont - Construction Progress, 1935 October-1935 November (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Fort Dupont - Construction Progress, 1936 January (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Fort Dupont - Construction Progress, 1936 February (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Fort Dupont - Construction Progress, 1936 March (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Fort Dupont - Construction Progress, 1936 May (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Fort Dupont - Construction Progress, 1936 July (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Fort Dupont - Construction Progress, 1936 December (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Fort Dupont - Construction Progress, 1937 April (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Fort Dupont - Construction Progress, 1937 September (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Fort Dupont - Construction Progress, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Fort Dupont - Construction Progress, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Fort Dupont/Fort Foote - Erosion Control, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Fort Dupont/Fort Foote - Erosion Control, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Fort Dupont - Fort Drive - Construction, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Fort Dupont - Mount Vernon Highway, 1933 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Fort Dupont - National Arboretum, 1934 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Fort Dupont - National Arboretum, 1934 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Fort Dupont - Roach Run, 1934 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Fort Dupont - Snow Removal, 1935 February (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Fort Dupont - Snow Removal, 1935 December (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Fort Dupont - Uniforms, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Fort Hunt - Athletics (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Fort Hunt - Baseball Team, 1935-1936 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Fort Hunt - National Capital Parks Basketball Team, 1935-1936 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Fort Hunt - Leiter Estate Picnic Area, 1937 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Fort Hunt - Planning Picnic Area, 1935 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - National Capital Parks Projects - Report, 1933-1941 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Rock Creek Park - Duke of Windsor Visit, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Duke of Windsor
- Campaigns and Drives
  - Back the Attack Show, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Bond Drive Launch, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Community Chest Launch, Treasury Department, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Community Chest Launch, US Capitol, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Keep Paper Off Park Areas Campaign, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - March of Dimes, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - OPA War Fund Drive, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Shot from the Sky Show, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - This is Your Infantry Bond Show, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Victory Bond/Iwo Jima Statue, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Weapons of War Exhibit, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Weapons of War Exhibit, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Carter Barron Amphitheater
  - Basement (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Construction, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    Negative Only
  - Construction, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Construction, 1950 March-1950 April (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Construction, 1950 May (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Construction, 1950 June (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Construction, 1950 July (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Construction, 1950 August (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Construction, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Construction, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Construction, 1952 November (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Construction - Ground Breaking, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Construction - Curtain Installation, 1953 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Construction - Grading, 1949-1950 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Construction - Guttering and Flashing (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Construction - Dressing Room, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Construction - Electrical Work (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Construction - Seating Area Cover (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Programs - American Music Festival, 1955 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Programs - Army Band Concert, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Programs - Army Band Concert, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Programs - Army Band Concert (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Programs - Ballet of Canada, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Programs - Ballet Russe de Monte Carlo, 19214 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Programs - Ballet Russe de Monte Carlo, 19225 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Programs - Ballet Russe de Monte Carlo, 1955 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Programs - Ballet Russe de Monte Carlo, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Programs - Benny Goodman, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Programs - Cab Calloway, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Programs - Carmen Amaya Dance Group, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Programs - "Carmen Jones" and Miss Washington Contest, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Programs - "Carousel", 1953 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Programs - "Dancing Waters", 1954 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Programs - Danny Kaye, 1956 June (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Programs - Danny Kaye, 1956 August (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Programs - Dedication, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Programs - Easter Sunrise Service, 1953 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Programs - "Faith of our Fathers", 1950 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Programs - "Faith of our Fathers", 1950 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Programs - "Faith of our Fathers", 1950 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Programs - General (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Programs - "Golden Apple", 1954 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Programs - "Ice Capades", 1955 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Programs - "Ice for Children" with Miss Washington, 1955 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Programs - Ice Cycles, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Programs - Jose Greco Dancers, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Programs - Jose Greco Dancers, 1955 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Programs - Jose Greco Dancers, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Programs - Louis Armstrong, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Programs - "Mikado", 1954 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Programs - "Mikado", 1956 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Programs - Miss Washington Contest, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Programs - National Ballet of Canada, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Programs - National Music Week, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Programs - National Music Week, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Programs - National Music Week, 1954 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Programs - Phoenix 55, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Programs - "Saint Bleecker Street", 1955 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Programs - "Showboat" Premiere, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Programs - Willard Hotel Luncheon, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Ticket Office, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Celebrities
  - 1938/1950 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - 1938/1950 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - President's Birthday Ball, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Children
  - Activities - "Wedding", 1948 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Activities - Coloring, 1931 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Condemnation and Demolition of Buildings
  - 18th to 19th Streets and C Street to Virginia Avenue, NW, 1937 April (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - 33rd Street, SE (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - 1500 Block of 34th Street, 1937 September 21 00:00:00 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - 48th and Nash Streets, NE, 1953 November 18 00:00:00 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - 415 55th Street, NE, 1953 December 28 00:00:00 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - 137 59th Street, NE, 1953 December 28 00:00:00 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - 1304 Alabama Avenue, SE, 1959 October 13 00:00:00 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - 4801-4807 Deane Avenue, NE, 1953 December 28-1959 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - 1814 Fairlawn Avenue, SE, 1954 September 14 00:00:00 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - 3200 Foxhall Road, NW, 1937 March 22 00:00:00 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - 4128 Gault Street, NE, 1937 September 1 00:00:00 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - 4215 Livingston Road, SE, 1953 December 28 00:00:00 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Maryland Avenue and 7th Street, NW, 1956 April 20 00:00:00 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - 4801 Minnesota Avenue, NE, 1953 November 18 00:00:00 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - 1805 Naylor Road. SE, 1954 September 14 00:00:00 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Newton Street, NE, 1953 July 30 00:00:00 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Portland and Nichols Avenue, SE, 1936 August 4 00:00:00 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - 133 Raleigh Street, SE, 1937 January 26 00:00:00 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - 2400 Block of T Street, SE (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - C & O Canal - 3600 Block K Street, NW, 1952 October 16-1953 April 24 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - C & O Canal - 3900 Block of K Street, NW, 1953 April 24 00:00:00 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - C & O Canal - 3900 K Street, NW, 1952 October 16-1955 December 15 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - C & O Canal - 3906 K Street, NW, 1952 October 16-1955 December 15 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - C & O Canal - 3910 K Street, NW, 1953 April 24-1954 April 9 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - C & O Canal - 3912 K Street, NW, 1952 October 16-1954 June 4 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - C & O Canal - 3914 K Street, NW, 1952 October 17-1953 October 2 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - C & O Canal - 4036 K Street, NW, 1952 October 16-1955 December 15 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - C & O Canal - 4100 K Street, NW, 1952 October 16-1955 December 15 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - C & O Canal - 4110 K Street, NW, 1953 October 2 00:00:00 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - C & O Canal - 4114-4120 K Street, NW, 1952 October 16-1953 April 24 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - C & O Canal - 4900 K Street, NW (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - C & O Canal - 4205 & 4207 Canal Road, NW, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - C & O Canal - 4216 Canal Road, NW, 1952-1953 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - C & O Canal - 4218 Canal Road, NW, 1952 October 16-1953 April 24 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - C & O Canal - 4219 Canal Road, NW, 1952 October 30-1953 June 4 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - C & O Canal - 4221 Canal Road, NW, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - C & O Canal - 4222 Canal Road, NW, 1952 October 30-1953 April 24 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - C & O Canal - 4500 Canal Road, NW, 1952 October 30-1953 April 24 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - C & O Canal - 4516 Canal Road, NW, 1952 October 17-1953 April 24 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - C & O Canal - 4518 Canal Road, NW, 1952 October 30-1953 April 24 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - C & O Canal - 4519 Canal Road, NW, 1952 October 30 00:00:00 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - C & O Canal - 4520 Canal Road, NW, 1952 October 30-1953 April 24 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - C & O Canal - 4521 Canal Road, NW, 1953 May 12-1954 June 4 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - C & O Canal - 4522 Canal Road, NW, 1952 October 30-1953 April 24 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - C & O Canal - 4524 Canal Road, NW, 1953 April 24 00:00:00 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - C & O Canal - 4527 Canal Road, NW, 1952 October 16 00:00:00 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - C & O Canal - 4902 Canal Road, NW, 1952 October 30-1954 June 4 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - C & O Canal - 4904 Canal Road, NW, 1952 October 30-1953 June 4 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - C & O Canal - 4906 Canal Road, NW, 1953 June 4 00:00:00 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - C & O Canal - 4910 Canal Road, NW, 1952 October 30-1953 June 4 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - C & O Canal - 4914 Canal Road, NW, 1953 June 4 00:00:00 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - C & O Canal - 4918 Canal Road, NW, 1953 June 4 00:00:00 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - C & O Canal - 4920 Canal Road, NW, 1952 October 17 00:00:00 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - C & O Canal - 4922 Canal Road, NW, 1953 June 4 00:00:00 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - C & O Canal - 4924 Canal Road, NW, 1952 October 16-1953 June 4. (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - C & O Canal - 4930 Canal Road, NW, 1952 October 16-1953 June 4 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - C & O Canal - 4950 Canal Road, NW, 1953 June 4-1957 October 30 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - C & O Canal - 4940 Canal Road, NW (Fletcher's Boat House), 1952 October 16-1953 June 4 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - C & O Canal - Canal Road at Chain Bridge, 1953 May 12-1953 June 4 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - C & O Canal - Canal Road North of Chain Bridge, 1952 October 16 00:00:00 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - C & O Canal - High Island, 1959 September 28 00:00:00 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - C & O Canal - 6620 MacArthur Boulevard - Brookmont, MD, 1954 January 29 00:00:00 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - C & O Canal - 6622 MacArthur Boulevard - Brookmont, MD, 1954 January 29 00:00:00 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - C & O Canal - 6644 MacArthur Boulevard - Brookmont, MD, 1954 January 29 00:00:00 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - C & O Canal - 6652 MacArthur Boulevard - Brookmont, MD, 1955 March 16 00:00:00 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - C & O Canal - 6654 MacArthur Boulevard - Brookmont, MD, 1954 January 29 00:00:00 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - C & O Canal - 6700 MacArthur Boulevard - Brookmont, MD, 1954 January 29 00:00:00 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - C & O Canal - 6714 MacArthur Boulevard - Brookmont, MD, 1954 January 29 00:00:00 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - C & O Canal - 6716 MacArthur Boulevard - Brookmont, MD, 1954 February 23 00:00:00 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - C & O Canal - 6718 MacArthur Boulevard - Brookmont, MD, 1955 March 10 00:00:00 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - C & O Canal - 6720 MacArthur Boulevard - Brookmont, MD, 1955 March 10 00:00:00 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - C & O Canal - 6734 MacArthur Boulevard - Brookmont, MD, 1955 March 10 00:00:00 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - C & O Canal - 6738 MacArthur Boulevard - Brookmont, MD, 1955 March 10 00:00:00 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - C & O Canal - 6740 MacArthur Boulevard - Brookmont, MD, 1955 March 10 00:00:00 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - C & O Canal - 6742 MacArthur Boulevard - Brookmont, MD, 1955 March 16 00:00:00 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - C & O Canal - 6748 MacArthur Boulevard - Brookmont, MD, 1955 March 10 00:00:00 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - C & O Canal - 6752 MacArthur Boulevard - Brookmont, MD, 1954 May 18 00:00:00 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - C & O Canal - 6802 MacArthur Boulevard - Brookmont, MD, 1954 May 18 00:00:00 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - C & O Canal - 6804 MacArthur Boulevard - Brookmont, MD, 1954 May 18 00:00:00 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - C & O Canal - 6806 MacArthur Boulevard - Brookmont, MD, 1954 May 18 00:00:00 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - C & O Canal - 6807 MacArthur Boulevard - Brookmont, MD, 1955 March 2-1955 March 16 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - C & O Canal - 6808 MacArthur Boulevard - Brookmont, MD, 1954 May 18 00:00:00 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - C & O Canal - 6815 MacArthur Boulevard - Brookmont, MD, 1955 March 2 00:00:00 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - C & O Canal - 6817 MacArthur Boulevard - Brookmont, MD, 1955 March 2 00:00:00 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - C & O Canal - 6817 1/2 MacArthur Boulevard - Brookmont, MD, 1955 March 2 00:00:00 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - C & O Canal - 6819 MacArthur Boulevard - Brookmont, MD, 1955 March 2 00:00:00 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - C & O Canal - 6825 MacArthur Boulevard - Brookmont, MD, 1955 March 2-1955 March 16 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - C & O Canal - 6829 MacArthur Boulevard - Brookmont, MD, 1955 March 2 00:00:00 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - C & O Canal - 6836 MacArthur Boulevard - Brookmont, MD, 1955 March 16 00:00:00 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - C & O Canal - 6900 MacArthur Boulevard - Brookmont, MD, 1955 March 16 00:00:00 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - C & O Canal - 6904 MacArthur Boulevard - Brookmont, MD, 1955 March 16 00:00:00 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - C & O Canal - 6908 MacArthur Boulevard - Brookmont, MD, 1955 March 16 00:00:00 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - C & O Canal - 6910 MacArthur Boulevard - Brookmont, MD, 1955 March 16 00:00:00 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - C & O Canal - 6912 MacArthur Boulevard - Brookmont, MD, 1954 February 23 00:00:00 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - C & O Canal - 6950 MacArthur Boulevard - Brookmont, MD, 1955 March 16 00:00:00 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - C & O Canal - 6960 MacArthur Boulevard - Brookmont, MD, 1955 March 16 00:00:00 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - C & O Canal - 7002 MacArthur Boulevard - Brookmont, MD, 1955 March 16 00:00:00 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - C & O Canal - 7011 MacArthur Boulevard - Brookmont, MD, 1953 March 26 00:00:00 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - C & O Canal - 7112 MacArthur Boulevard - Brookmont, MD, 1955 March 16 00:00:00 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - C & O Canal - 7142 MacArthur Boulevard - Brookmont, MD, 1953 March 26 00:00:00 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - C & O Canal - 7220 MacArthur Boulevard - Brookmont, MD, 1957 October 30 00:00:00 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - C & O Canal - MacArthur Boulevard - Brookmont, MD, 1954 May 18-1954 May 28 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - C & O Canal - 6301 Potomac Drive - Brookmont, MD, 1954 September 15 00:00:00 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - C & O Canal - 6303 Potomac Drive - Brookmont, MD, 1954 March 5 00:00:00 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - C & O Canal - 6307 Potomac Drive - Brookmont, MD, 1953 July 9-1954 March 2 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - C & O Canal - 6372 Potomac Drive - Brookmont, MD, 1954 March 2 00:00:00 (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - C & O Canal - 6403 Potomac Drive - Brookmont, MD, 1952 November 17 00:00:00 (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - C & O Canal - 6417 Potomac Drive - Brookmont, MD, 1954 September 15 00:00:00 (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - C & O Canal - 6421 Potomac Drive - Brookmont, MD, 1954 March 5 00:00:00 (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - C & O Canal - 6505 Potomac Drive - Brookmont, MD, 1954 March 8 00:00:00 (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - C & O Canal - 6515 Potomac Drive - Brookmont, MD, 1954 March 8 00:00:00 (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - C & O Canal - 6519 Potomac Drive - Brookmont, MD, 1954 March 8 00:00:00 (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - C & O Canal - 6521 Potomac Drive - Brookmont, MD, 1954 September 15 00:00:00 (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - C & O Canal - 6525 Potomac Drive - Brookmont, MD, 1954 March 8 00:00:00 (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - C & O Canal - 6601 Potomac Drive - Brookmont, MD, 1954 September 15 00:00:00 (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - C & O Canal - 6603 Potomac Drive - Brookmont, MD, 1954 September 15 00:00:00 (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - C & O Canal - 6607 Potomac Drive - Brookmont, MD, 1954 March 8 00:00:00 (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - C & O Canal - 6619 Potomac Drive - Brookmont, MD, 1954 February 23 00:00:00 (Box 8, Folder 59)
  - C & O Canal - 6620 Potomac Drive - Brookmont, MD, 1953 October 2 00:00:00 (Box 8, Folder 60)
  - C & O Canal - 6621 Potomac Drive - Brookmont, MD, 1953 November 10 00:00:00 (Box 8, Folder 61)
  - C & O Canal - 6633 Potomac Drive - Brookmont, MD, 1954 April 9 00:00:00 (Box 8, Folder 62)
  - C & O Canal - 6635 Potomac Drive - Brookmont, MD, 1953 October 2 00:00:00 (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - C & O Canal - 6639 Potomac Drive - Brookmont, MD, 1954 April 9 00:00:00 (Box 8, Folder 64)
  - C & O Canal - 6745 Potomac Drive - Brookmont, MD, 1953 December 7 00:00:00 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - C & O Canal - 6747 Potomac Drive - Brookmont, MD, 1953 April 9 00:00:00 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - C & O Canal - 6749 Potomac Drive - Brookmont, MD, 1954 April 9 00:00:00 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - C & O Canal - 6751 Potomac Drive - Brookmont, MD, 1953 July 7 00:00:00 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - C & O Canal - 6753 Potomac Drive - Brookmont, MD, 1954 March 8 00:00:00 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - C & O Canal - 6754 Potomac Drive - Brookmont, MD, 1953 October 2 00:00:00 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - C & O Canal - 6755 Potomac Drive - Brookmont, MD, 1954 March 8 00:00:00 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - C & O Canal - 6758 Potomac Drive - Brookmont, MD, 1953 October 2 00:00:00 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - C & O Canal - 6000 Ridge Drive - Brookmont, MD, 1954 April 9 00:00:00 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - C & O Canal - 6006 Ridge Drive - Brookmont, MD, 1954 April 9 00:00:00 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - C & O Canal - 6020 Ridge Drive - Brookmont, MD, 1954 January 21 00:00:00 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - C & O Canal - 6022 Ridge Drive - Brookmont, MD, 1954 January 29 00:00:00 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - C & O Canal - 6026 Ridge Drive - Brookmont, MD, 1955 March 10 00:00:00 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - C & O Canal - 6030 Ridge Drive - Brookmont, MD, 1953 March 26 00:00:00 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - C & O Canal - 6032 Ridge Drive - Brookmont, MD, 1955 March 10 00:00:00 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - C & O Canal - 6034 Ridge Drive - Brookmont, MD, 1955 March 10 00:00:00 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - C & O Canal - 6040 Ridge Drive - Brookmont, MD, 1955 March 10 00:00:00 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - C & O Canal - 6202 Ridge Drive - Brookmont, MD, 1954 March 2 00:00:00 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - C & O Canal - 6208 Ridge Drive - Brookmont, MD, 1955 March 10 00:00:00 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - C & O Canal - 6300 Ridge Drive - Brookmont, MD, 1953 March 26 00:00:00 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - C & O Canal - 6372 Ridge Drive - Brookmont, MD, 1954 March 2 00:00:00 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - C & O Canal - 6400 Ridge Drive - Brookmont, MD, 1954 March 2 00:00:00 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - C & O Canal - 6400 78th Street - Cabin John, MD, 1955 December 15-1957 October 30 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - C & O Canal - 6407 78th Street - Cabin John, MD, 1955 December 15 00:00:00 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - C & O Canal - 6405 83rd Place - Cabin John, MD, 1953 March 26 00:00:00 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - C & O Canal - 8207 83rd Street - Cabin John, MD, 1957 October 30 00:00:00 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - C & O Canal - 7004 Riverside Avenue - Cabin John, MD, 1955 December 15 00:00:00 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - C & O Canal - 7800 Riverside Avenue - Cabin John, MD, 1955 December 15 00:00:00 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - C & O Canal - 7802 Riverside Avenue - Cabin John, MD, 1955 December 15 00:00:00 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - C & O Canal - 7806 Riverside Avenue - Cabin John, MD, 1955 December 15 00:00:00 (Box 9, Folder 30)